Guide to the Sarah Elbert papers, 1968-1976.
Elbert, Sarah papers, 1968-1976
- Series VII. Videos
  - "The Streets Belong to the People" (Copy, 36.5min version), VHS V-49a (Box 3)
  - "The Streets Belong to the People" (29min version), VHS V-50 (Box 3)
  - "The Streets Belong to the People" Out takes, no sound, VHS V-208 (Box 3)
  - "The American Experience: Chicago 1968", VHS V-238 (Box 3)
    Videocassette of "The American Experience: Chicago 1968," a narrated story of the 1968 Democratic National Convention and related demonstrations and riots by the "Yippies." Footage includes Democratic National Convention, protestors at the "Festival of Life" (Grant and Lincoln Parks), and resulting riots. Includes scenes from "The Streets Belong to the People."
  - "The Streets Belong to the People" (Copy, 29min version), Betacam SP V-441 (Box 5)
    Copy of F-1090-1091
- Series VIII. CDs and DVDs (Copies of other materials in the collection)
  - Bacia Gordon interviewed by Susan Schultze, August 27, 1969 (1968), CD-21 (Box 5)
    Immediate recall of events in Grant Park.
    Copy of tr-268-5.
  - Copies of tr-268 no 1, 9, 10, 12, 14-16, 18-23, 27-33; 35-36, CD-45-75 (Box 5)
    See above list of reel to reel recordings for more information.
  - "The Streets Belong to the People", DVD-18 (Box 5)
    Copies of film reels F-159-162